{
    "id": "c2de763d15824c4199b0587d88a1e2a8",
    "title": "Formation of questions",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "b3d155e0a8ba4996b9804ff29bc1dd81",
            "title": "Formation Of Questions",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": ".................................... she have a sister?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Does",
                        "Do",
                        "Has"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "....................................... you have meetings on Mondays?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Had",
                        "Do",
                        "Does"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "......................................... Jack speak many languages?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Does",
                        "Do",
                        "Has"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": ".......................................... she ever speak rudely?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Do",
                        "Does",
                        "Has"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "........................................ your kids like to watch TV?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Do",
                        "Does",
                        "Have"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "........................................ she like him?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Does",
                        "Do"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "............................................. you often have meetings on Thursdays?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Does",
                        "Have",
                        "Do"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "..................................... it rain here in winter?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Does",
                        "Do"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": ".......................................... he play the guitar well?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Do",
                        "Does"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "......................................... you believe in his integrity?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Do",
                        "Does",
                        "Have"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "....................................... the elephant have a trunk?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Do",
                        "Does"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "What ........................................ James deal in?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "do",
                        "does",
                        "have"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Where ........................................... she work?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "do",
                        "does"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}